（小関(おぜき)）みんな…
You guys...
（桐仁(きりひと)）泣くには まだ早いよ 部長
It's too early for tears, captain.
Yeah, it's not over yet.
ああ　まだ終わってない
潮(うしお)　勝ってほしい！
Ushio, I want you to win.
It's now your turn to have
your hard work rewarded.
次は お前が報われる番だぞ
Here I go.
（火ノ丸(ひのまる)）行ってくる
Bout 9
"Demon and Moon"
（咲(さき)）
いよいよ国宝同士の一戦
Time for the two national treasures
to go toe-to-toe.
Bato-san. Enoki-san. Watch closely.
バトさん 榎木(えのき)さん
しっかり見ておいてね
（バトムンフ）
フン…　見る意味ない
There's no need.
They might be national treasures,
（榎木）国宝同士といったって
天王寺(てんのうじ)主将とは格が違う
but they're not in the same
league as Captain Tennoji.
（狩谷(かりや)）ンンッ…　アアッ…
（狩谷）あ〜 見えねえよ！
（ダニエル）うん？
I can't see a thing.
Daniel, what are you doing? Put me down!
ダニエル　何すんだ やめろ！
You said you couldn't see, Shun-san.
（ダニエル）
だって 俊(しゅん)さん 見えない
（狩谷）いいから はな…
（アナウンス）インターハイ
Never mind! Just put—
The final bout of the Inter High
Chiba Prefectural team competition.
千葉県予選 団体　決勝 大将戦
西 潮君
On the west side, Ushio-kun.
東 沙田(さだ)君
On the east side, Sada-kun.
Our place at nationals hinges on this bout.
（荒木(あらき)）全国行けるかどうか
次で決まるのか
（間宮(まみや)）うるせえよ 荒木
（荒木）あっ…
Shut up, Araki.
Sorry, Sada.
（真田(さなだ)）悪いな 沙田
I didn't want to pile this
much pressure on a first-year.
１年のお前に
背負わせたくはなかったんだが
Onimaru's strong, for sure,
but you're Ishi High's ace.
（金盛(かなもり)）鬼丸(おにまる)は強い
だが お前は石(いし)高のエースだ
ビシッと決めてこい！
Go show him what you can do!
Don't you worry.
（沙田）大丈夫ッスよ
I'll take our team to nationals.
俺がチームを
全国に連れていきますから
Award
First Place
I've always had total confidence
in my athletic abilities.
（沙田）
昔から運動神経には自信があった
National
Elementary
School
Sumo
Tournament
Y'know... I've never given sumo a go.
（少年時代の沙田）
そういえば—
相撲は
やったことなかったな
（女の子）えっ？　沙田君が相撲？
Sada-kun, a sumo wrestler?
Don't do it.
（女の子）やめてよ！
廻(まわ)し姿なんてカッコ悪い
No one looks good in a mawashi belt.
（歓声）
（少年時代の沙田）じゃ もし—
So does that mean...
そんな廻し姿でも
カッコよく見えたら そいつは…
if some guy did rock a mawashi belt,
he'd be the coolest guy ever?
本当に
カッコいいヤツなんだろうな
Because you wear nothing but a belt,
（沙田）何も着けないからこそ
肌から じかに伝わる殺気
you can feel the intensity
coursing through your skin.
I really took to sumo, way more
than I ever thought I would.
相撲は思いのほか 性に合っていた
I wanted to fight all-out against an
opponent who shone as brightly as he did.
あのくらいギラついた相手と
ギリギリの勝負をしたい
National Middle School Sumo Tournament
Individual
Champion
なのに…
But...
as I climbed the ranks and attained
the title of "middle school yokozuna,"
中学横綱まで
上り詰めた その土俵に—
the opponent I wanted
to face wasn't in the ring.
望む相手は いなかった
（礼奈(れいな)）ンッ…
You know what I heard?
（舟木）俺 聞いたけど
あの沙田ってヤツの廻しは—
This Sada guy's belt is pristine
'cause no one can lay a finger on it.
誰も触れないから真っ白なんだって
Seriously?
（橋）マジかよ？
（舟木）実際 この大会中 誰にも…
No one's managed to grab it
this tournament, either.
（西郷）
おい　そんなヤツに勝てんのか？
Whoa...
Can Hinomaru beat someone like that?
Onimaru Kunitsuna versus
Mikazuki Munechika.
（咲）鬼丸国綱(くにつな) 対 三日月宗近(みかづきむねちか)
A bout contested by national treasures.
（咲）国宝同士の対決
（桐仁）ンッ…
Spirit!
（審判）はっきよい！
Their charges...
（小関）立ち合いは…
（金盛）互角
...canceled each other out.
Onimaru used a thrust and shove?
鬼丸が突き押し？
At that range, Sada-kun has the advantage.
（柴木山(しばきやま)）
それは 沙田君の得意な間合いだ
You...
この！
His arm holds are a real nuisance!
やはり うっとうしいのぅ
このおっつけは
In that case...
なら…
（突く音）
How do you like this?!
これで どうじゃ！
His slaps are getting faster!
（小関）回転数が上がっていく！
（佑真(ゆうま)）速(はえ)え！
They're a blur!
I don't need to block every strike.
（沙田）全てをさばく必要はない
The hard strikes with
real weight behind them
体重の乗った本物の突きの中に
押し気のない突きが混じっている
are interspersed with light strikes.
その真偽を見極めて…
I can figure out which is which
（火ノ丸）アッ！
（沙田）リアルのみ切って落とす！
and only counter the hard hits!
（蛍(けい)）はたかれた！
（小関）危ない！
He slapped his hand away!
Watch out!
He's going even faster now!
更に回転数が上がっている
I can't tell which is which.
（沙田）真偽が見えない！
全ての突きに気迫が込められている
Every strike has power behind it!
Hey...
おい…
沙田が笑ってる
Sada's smiling.
This is fun.
（沙田）楽しいよ　この緊張感
ずっと こんな勝負がしたかった
This sense of uncertainty.
I've been waiting for a fight like this!
And what about you, Onimaru?
なあ 鬼丸　君も そうだろう？
I know you've wanted this, too!
（火ノ丸）何を笑っていやがる
What are you grinning about?!
I'm only going to smile
（火ノ丸）ワシが笑うのは…
てめえの首を取ったあとじゃ！
once I've taken your head!
He grabbed his arm!
（蛍）逆に おっつけた！
（千比路(ちひろ)）しゃ！　いけ〜！
That's it! Get him!
Sada switched to strikes?
沙田が突っ張り？
Onimaru can't get close to him!
鬼丸が近づけない！
（突く音）
なんてキレのあるシャープな突き
What sharp, knife-like strikes.
ンンッ…
１発１発 的確に体を押し上げる
Each strike is precisely
targeted to push him back.
You were the one who dragged Yuma
and the others into this sport.
（礼奈）
あんたが 佑真や みんなを—
この世界に
引きずり込んだんでしょう
They're here because they believe in you!
みんな あんたを信じて
ここまで来たんだよ
Win, Hinomaru!
勝てよ 火ノ丸！
Crescent Moon!
（沙田）下弦の月！
（礼奈）あっ！
（火ノ丸）
この瞬間を待っとったぜ！
I've been waiting for you to do that!
He moved into Sada's throw!
沙田の出し投げに追いついた！
（３人）あっ！
（礼奈）つかんだ！
He grabbed him!
Demon Wheel!
三日月の野郎…
That Mikazuki...
When did he stop his throwing motion?
いつの間に上手(うわて)を引いてやがった？
ハァ…
息つく暇なんてねえぜ！
You don't have time to huff and puff!
Here's my second counterattack...
返す刀の ふた太刀目！
鬼嵐(おにあらし)！
Demon Storm!
He's still standing after that?!
あれを耐えるのかよ！
His Demon Storm didn't work, either!
鬼嵐も封じられた！
I knew that wouldn't be enough to win!
（火ノ丸）
これで勝てるとは思ってねえよ！
Hundred Demon Takedown!
Hundred
Demon
Take
Down
He's strong...
（沙田）強いな　これが鬼丸国綱
This is Onimaru Kunitsuna.
誰よりも小さいはずの その体が
今まで戦った誰より大きく見える
He's got the smallest body going, but he
stands taller than anyone I've ever fought.
ずっと
こんな相手と戦える日を待っていた
I've been waiting for the day I could
compete with someone like him.
But are you satisfied with just competing?
戦えただけで満足か？
Of course it isn't!
…んなわけねえだろう！
What I really seek
俺が求めたのは…
強者からの勝利！
is victory against the strong!
Sada's... roaring.
沙田が ほえた…
（火ノ丸）ンンッ…
（沙田）上弦の月！
First Quarter Moon!
（蛍）ウワッ！　喉輪(のどわ)！
He's got his throat!
Sada's being unusually aggressive.
沙田が あんなに強引に行くとは…
あいつの あんな顔 初めて見た
I've never seen that look in his eyes before.
He pulled away?!
そこで退(ひ)くのかよ！
Th-They're moving so fast,
I can't tell what's going on.
（橋）は… 速すぎて何が何だか…
So this is a battle between
national treasures.
（舟木）これが国宝同士の戦い…
ヤアッ！
Just by placing his hand below his arm...
（寺原(てらはら)）下から あてがうだけで…
（柴木山）突きの威力を殺した
...he took the power out of the strike.
Sada-kun's signature power arm grab.
沙田君の強力なおっつけ
There's nothing Onimaru can do?
あの鬼丸が なすすべなしかよ
But he's still got that new technique.
（佑真）でも まだ新技がある
He can use the triple combo.
（蛍）３つの合わせ技が
あるじゃないですか
His new technique isn't ready yet.
（桐仁）
新技は まだ完成していない
There wasn't enough time to
perfect it before the tournament.
この県大会には間に合わなかった
（佑真）沙田相手に
新技なしで勝てるのか？
Can he beat Sada without it?
He's got this.
（千比路）決めるぜ
He faces down adversity
and draws power from it!
あいつは 逆境を力に変える男だ！
（火ノ丸）お〜らぁ！
He grabbed both sides of the belt!
（男性）両廻し 引いた！
That's it. Believe, Hinomaru.
（桐仁）そうだ　信じろ 火ノ丸
As you chase your wild dream
of becoming a pro yokozuna
大相撲の横綱になるなんていう
お前の無謀な夢に—
and train like a madman, your body
has never betrayed you, so believe in it!
つらい稽古に泣き言 言わずに
ついてきた その体を！
（火ノ丸）
こいつには百鬼薙(ひゃっきな)ぎじゃ足りん
The Hundred Demon Takedown
isn't enough for this guy!
If I don't beat this guy,
I'm not worthy of becoming a yokozuna!
ここで決めねえで
なにが横綱じゃ！
I will win and grin from ear to ear...
勝って 最後に笑うのは…
He cut him off!
出鼻を…
You're taking risks because
you actually think you can win.
（沙田）
勝機があるから 君もムチャをする
But your fun stops here.
もう何もさせない
I'm the only one who needs
to shine in this ring!
土俵で輝くのは俺だけでいい！
That's...
あれは…
Own Hand Pulling Overarm Throw!
Own Hand Pulling
Overarm Throw
Double Moon!
Double
Moon
The lingering feeling of something
other than my feet touching the sand...
（火ノ丸）
足裏以外に まとわりつく砂の感触
And everyone looking down at me...
みんながワシを見下ろす
My feet feel heavy.
足が重い　ヘドロの中を
進んでいるような不快感
Like I'm sinking into sickening sludge.
People had come to cheer me on.
期待してくれる人もいた
I didn't want them seeing me like that.
こんなカッコ悪いところ
見られたくなかった
Don't look at me... Mom!
ワシを見んでくれ　母ちゃん
Have I gone as far as I can?
（火ノ丸）
ワシは もう やり尽くしたのか？
Is this all I can do?
何もできず このまま…
おい　やめろ
Hey, stop that...
（桐仁）なんで そんな顔…
Why are you making that face?
I envy you.
（火ノ丸）ホレボレするよ
恵まれた その体　才能
I envy your body and talent.
If you end up going pro, I bet
you'll go on to do great things.
きっと お前は大相撲に行っても
大成するんじゃろう
You were destined to become a yokozuna.
生まれたときから横綱になる運命(さだめ)
I guess... I wasn't.
ワシは そうじゃなかった
Like hell I wasn't!
（火ノ丸）ふざけるな！
His arm!
腕が…
Hinomaru...
火ノ丸…
Talent? Destiny?
（火ノ丸）
才能？　運命？　うるせえよ！
It's all just noise!
No one gets to decide my future but me!
誰にも決めさせねえ！
ワシが相撲に…
I've already mapped it out for myself!
（はじく音）
決めたんじゃ！
（小関）か… 返した！
He struck back!
（火ノ丸）いいよ
I'm fine with losing to you at
talent for sumo and all that stuff.
相撲の才能とか
そういうのは全部 お前の勝ちで
But as far as this bout goes...
この勝負の勝ちだけは—
Victory will be mine!
ここに置いていけ！
What?!
（間宮）なに！？
（佑真）取った！
He grabbed on!
This underhand position...
（沙田）この下手(したて)は…
This is dangerous!
危険だ！　断ち切る！
I have to cut it off!
右肘はマズイ！
Not his right elbow!
The optimal distance.
（柴木山）最適な間 足さばき
The footwork.
必殺の形！
That unbeatable form!
I don't want to lose!
負けたくない！
（桐仁）新技は…
His new technique
３点同時攻撃だ！
is an attack on three points at once!
They're watching...
（火ノ丸）見とるぞ
お天道(てんとう)さまが…　みんなが！
The sun's watching,
and so's everyone else!
They've seen your resolve!
みんなの覚悟を…
情熱を…
Your passion!
激闘を…
Your fight!
今度はワシが見せる番じゃ！
Now, I'll show you the road that lies ahead
after I beat Sada, after we beat Ishi High!
沙田に… 石高に勝った その先を！
This is the final blow that
carries our destiny on its shoulders!
これがワシらの命運を乗せた
最後のひと太刀…
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop!
Hundred
Thou
sand
Demon
Drop
West side wins!
（審判）西の勝ち！
Yeah!
Ushio...
潮…
You did it, Ushio!
やったな 潮！
（火ノ丸）ハァハァ…　フゥ…
The final result: with a score of 3-2,
Odachi High School, on the west side, wins.
（アナウンス）以上をもちまして
３対２で 西 大太刀(おおだち)高校の勝ち
The Chiba Inter High preliminary
champions are Odachi High School!
インターハイ
千葉県予選 団体 優勝は—
大太刀高校に決定しました！
（舟木）ウオ〜ッ！
ホントに優勝しちまった！
Yeah!
They really did it!
Yuma-san's going to nationals!
（西郷）佑真さん 全国だ〜！
（笑い声）
（小関）潮！
（礼奈）みんな すごいな
They're all incredible.
O-Oh, right.
（桐仁）そ… そうだ！
How's your right arm?
右腕は大丈夫なのか？
（桐仁）“うん？”じゃねえよ！
ムチャしやがって
Don't give me that!
You're so reckless.
You could have dislocated it.
脱臼してても
おかしくなかったぞ！
Honestly.
…たく
Kirihito.
（火ノ丸）桐仁
（桐仁）うん？
（火ノ丸）
お前は うろたえすぎじゃ
You panic too much.
（桐仁）なに？
What?
As our gaffer, you need to be more stoic.
（火ノ丸）監督なら
もっと どっしり構えとかんか
Yeah, Prof here wasn't
much help in the final bouts.
確かに決勝のハカセは
かなり頼りなかったぜ
He did the biggest victory pose, too.
（小関）ガッツポーズも
誰よりも大きかったしな
ウッ クッ…
さすがに澄ましていられねえって
Well, I could hardly show no reaction.
（桐仁）何つうの？
I mean, it sort of felt like...
（桐仁）例えるなら…
（２人）うん？
Uh, what was my line again?
（千比路）え〜っと…
Like I was a mother watching
my children in a school play.
（桐仁）自分の子供たちが
学芸会で演じてるのを—
見守る母親の気分っつうか…
（佑真）ハフッ…
（蛍）ウワッ！
What the heck?
（千比路）何だ？　そりゃ
（小関）
分かるような分からんような…
I'm not sure if I get it or not.
（男性）おめでとう！
（火ノ丸）あっ…
（観客たち）おめでとう！
そっか　俺たち 優勝したんだな
Oh, right. We won, didn't we?
（火ノ丸）
今日で引退なんかさせねえよ
We won't let today's bouts be your last.
まずは県予選　そして 全国！
We're gonna breeze through the
prefectural prelims and go to nationals!
つきあってもらうぜ
てっぺんまで！
You're coming with us all the way to the top.
次は全国だな！
Next up, it's nationals!
おう！
Yeah!
最後の投げ
That last throw...
右腕が万全でないことを
瞬時に判断して—
He realized in that moment
that his right arm couldn't take it,
腕をたたんで 体全体で投げた
so he tucked it in and used his whole body.
しかし あんな いびつな形
頭では たどりつけねえよ
Nobody could think to take up such an
awkward stance. It had to be instinct.
フッ…　まったく
どこまで強くなりやがる
Damn, man, how strong are you gonna get?
フゥ…
結局 ここまで１勝もできなかった
I wasn't able to win a single bout.
I didn't contribute to our victory at all.
僕は この優勝に
何ひとつ貢献していない
今は お互い お荷物かもしれねえが
全国では いいところ見せようぜ
We might both be dead weight right now,
but let's show 'em all what
we can do at nationals.
Okay.
はい！
Every bout was important,
even the ones they lost.
（柴木山）
ムダな戦いなど一戦もなかったよ
敗戦さえもな
When one guy was defeated, their feelings
transfer on to the next person.
たとえ敗れても
その思いは次の者へと託された
And they in turn drew
strength from those feelings.
そして 紡がれた思いの束が
戦う者の力となる
土俵に上がる身は１人だが
誰も心は“独り”ではなかったよ
While only one wrestler entered the ring,
none of them were alone at heart.
（寺原）そうですね
Yeah, exactly.
If this hadn't been a team competition,
the bouts may have ended differently.
（柴木山）
もし これが団体戦でなければ—
それぞれの戦いの結末が
変わっていたかもしれん
もちろん 負けたほうの思いが
弱かったかというと—
And you certainly can't accuse the losing
team of fighting with any less passion.
それは断じて違うがな
（拍手）
ウフフフッ…　優勝かぁ
We won!
Smiling, crying and eating,
all at the same time...
（佑真）笑い泣きで弁当食って
忙しいヤツだな
Huh? Kunisaki-san's not here?
（蛍）あれ？　國崎(くにさき)さんがいない
潮　その腕…
Ushio, your arm...
（火ノ丸）
いや　大したことはないんじゃがな
Oh, it's nothing serious.
I've stuck ice on it as a precaution.
大事を取って冷やしとる
I'm certainly glad it wasn't serious for us.
本当に大したことなくて
良かったよ ウチは
Ishigami
His right shoulder was partially dislocated.
（間宮）右肩の亜脱臼
ヒビが入ってるかもって
There may also be a hairline fracture.
I'm sorry I couldn't raise my game
to the standard expected of me.
（沙田）先輩方に
カッコ悪いとこ見せて すみません
After being lauded as a national
treasure and our team's ace,
国宝だ エースだと
さんざんもてはやされたあげく—
I let you down.
このザマです
真田さんや金盛主将たちの夏を—
It's my fault that
the third years' summer is over.
このチームの
戦いを終わらせたのは俺です
It's my fault that
the team's fight ended here.
責任取って 俺 相撲部を…
To apologize, I'll give—
How are you feeling right now,
Mr. National Treasure?
お前は今 どんな気持ちだ？
国宝さま
Disappointed.
悔しいッス
I'm pathetic.
情けなくて…
I'm going to make a selfish request.
（金盛）お前に わがままを
ひと言 言わせてもらう
最低でも あと２年は
石高相撲部に尽くせ
Spend the next two years
in the Ishi High sumo club.
He's right.
そうだぜ　残された俺らが
石高最強チームを作るんだからよ
Once they're gone, we're gonna need
to make Ishi High's team even stronger.
Mamiya-san...
間宮さん…
（真田）つうか 今日
やっと本気になったヤツに—
And you can't say you gave it your all
when you only got serious today.
やりきった感 出されてもな
（金盛）フッ…　まったくだぜ
You got that right.
Sada, your sumo journey
is only just starting.
沙田　お前の相撲は これからだ
We leave Ishi High in your hands.
石高を頼んだぞ
はい
Yes, sir.
How...
（荒木）なんで… なんで みんな
そんなに前向きなんですか？
How are you all thinking ahead already?
負けたのに…
We lost!
We lost because of me!
俺のせいで負けたのに！
You're all thinking it, aren't you?
みんなも
そう思ってるんでしょう？
Just come out and say it!
はっきり言ってくださいよ！
Araki...
（真田）荒木
（荒木）うん？
We lost because of you.
お前のせいで負けた
（荒木）ウワ〜ッ！
真田さんが明るいのが
いちばん納得いかねえ！
The fact that you're so cheery
makes the least sense to me!
（真田）ハハハハッ…　お前さんが
あんまり泣きじゃくるもんだから
You're blubbering so much,
I had to hold back the tears myself.
涙は引っ込んじまったよ
（咲）
なっ？　見に来て良かったやろう？
See? You're glad you came, right?
I told you Ushio Hinomaru-kun
was something special, didn't I?
潮火ノ丸君
ただ者じゃないって言うたやろう
データは取れた
I've got the data.
He's no match for Tennoji, but he'll
be glad we filmed the bouts for him.
天王寺兄貴の敵じゃないけど
でも きっと喜ぶ
I should be the one to give
the footage to Captain Tennoji.
天王寺主将に渡すなら
僕を通してもらおう
ンッ…　ヤダよ！
なんで お前に？
No way. Why should you get to do it?
Just give it to me!
（榎木）いいから よこせ！
What are you doing? Stop!
（バトムンフ）何する？　やめろ！
Saki-chan!
（寺原）咲ちゃん！
（咲）うん？
（咲）あっ 親方！
（榎木たち）えっ？
Master!
Shhh. I'm undercover.
しっ！　今日は お忍びなんだから
バレバレですって
Everyone knows who you are.
柴木山親方だ
It's Master Shibakiyama.
K-Kaoruyama?
か… 薫山(かおるやま)
Hinomaru's so strong.
（ダニエル）火ノ丸 強かった
（狩谷）ハァ〜ッ…
Even stronger than when he fought Sosuke.
（ダニエル）
草介(そうすけ)と戦ったときより強くなってる
フン！　草介は 更に強くなってる
Sosuke's gotten stronger, too.
I'm glad I came to Dachi High.
（千比路）ダチ高に入って良かった
I found sumo.
こうして相撲と出会えて
仲間たちと団体戦優勝までできた
I found teammates with whom
I won a team competition.
My only regret
ただひとつ惜しいのは—
いちばん戦いてえヤツが
身内にいるってことだ
is that the guy I want to
fight most is on my team.
The individual competition?
個人戦？　このあと？
It's starting now?
You're still worn out from the
team competition. Are you crazy?
団体戦 終わったばっかで
疲れてんのに バカなの？
I don't think I'm crazy,
but I am worn out, yeah.
（佑真）バカっつうか…
まあ 実際 疲れたわな
（小関）
でも 沙田が棄権となると—
But if Sada isn't competing...
Given that Ushio has to win
the individual competition as well,
個人戦でも
優勝しないといけない—
潮にとっては
言い方は あれだけど ありがたいな
this is lucky, even if
that's not a great thing to say.
Yeah! Hinomaru-san's sure to win!
（蛍）ですよね
火ノ丸さんなら もう楽勝ですよ！
Sure to win?
楽勝？　いや…
No...
I wouldn't say that.
そうでもねえよ
（小関）あっ…　國崎？
Kunisaki?
It has to be a serious bout.
（千比路）真剣勝負じゃなきゃ
手に入れられねえ
My dream of becoming the strongest
fighter lies beyond your fallen body.
お前を倒した先に
俺の“最強”という夢がある
H-Hey...
（小関）お… おい
（火ノ丸）当然じゃな
Of course.
I have no intention of taking
the easy way to the top.
ワシとて お膳立てしてもらって
頂点に立つ気など毛頭ない
That goes for the rest of you as well.
The gate to the summit is open to all.
みんなにも言えることじゃ
頂点は等しく開かれておる
そして ワシは
真剣勝負の土俵の上で—
And I...
I plan to take everything
everyone has to give
and win to be recognized as the best.
頂点に立って
認めてもらうつもりじゃ
（桐仁）
最高の仲間たちも 半刻(はんとき)後には…
Your best friends may,
in the next moment,
最大の敵となる
become your greatest enemies.
I figured you'd say that...
お前なら
そう言ってくれると思ったぜ
Onimaru Kunitsuna!
（千比路）鬼丸国綱！
It's been so long since
I signed an autograph.
（柴木山）サインなんて久しぶり
T-Tell him...
（バトムンフ）
す… “好きです”って—
（バトムンフ）伝えて
（咲）え〜っ？
...I love him.
Next Bout        "Unyielding Feelings"
Tell him yourself.
（榎木）自分で言えよ